Assassin. Hero. Legend.
The Warrior's Way is a adventure, fantasy, action
film directed by Lee Seung-moo.
A warrior-assassin is forced to hide in a small town in the
American Badlands after refusing a mission.
Yang, played by Jang Dong-gun.
Lynne, played by Kate Bosworth.
Ron, played by Geoffrey Rush.
Colonel, played by Danny Huston.
Saddest Flute, played by Ti Lung.
Eight-Ball, played by Tony Cox.
The Warrior's Way is a 2010 New Zealand-South Korean fantasy action film written and directed by Sngmoo
Lee and starring Jang Dong-gun, Kate Bosworth, Geoffrey Rush, Danny Huston and Tony Cox.
The film was released on 3 December 2010.
Its plot concerns a 19th-century warrior named Yang (Jang Dong-gun), who is
ordered to kill the last member of an enemy clan — a baby girl.
He refuses the mission and flees with the child to a
dilapidated town in the American West.
The film explores themes of small town, assassin, forest, deception, revenge.
The tone is intense.